{
  "title": "Assessment: Characteristics & Grouping of Materials",
  "categories": ["Shape", "Mass", "Volume", "Color", "Ability to Flow"],
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "Which one has a different shape?",
      "choices": ["Basketball", "Globe", "Marble", "Box"],
      "correctAnswer": 3,
      "category": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Which object is heavier than a book?",
      "choices": ["Feather", "Balloon", "Chair", "Pencil"],
      "correctAnswer": 2,
      "category": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Which occupies the most space?",
      "choices": ["Apple", "Watermelon", "Banana", "Banana"],
      "correctAnswer": 1,
      "category": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Which one has a different color?",
      "choices": ["Grass", "Corn", "Cheese", "Sun"],
      "correctAnswer": 0,
      "category": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "Which object has no definite shape?",
      "choices": ["Sand", "Water", "Clothes", "Bread"],
      "correctAnswer": 1,
      "category": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "It is the ability of an object to move in a continuous way.",
      "choices": ["Flow", "Wind", "Smooth", "Air"],
      "correctAnswer": 0,
      "category": 4
    },
    {
      "question": "Oil takes the shape of its container.",
      "choices": ["True", "False"],
      "correctAnswer": 0,
      "category": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "A weighing scale can measure an object's mass.",
      "choices": ["True", "False"],
      "correctAnswer": 0,
      "category": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Volume is the amount of space an object occupies.",
      "choices": ["True", "False"],
      "correctAnswer": 0,
      "category": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Grass, frogs, and bananas all have the same color.",
      "choices": ["True", "False"],
      "correctAnswer": 1,
      "category": 3
    }
  ]
}
